http://www.soundproofing.org/infopages/privacy.htm

tech:(760) 752-3030
"Categories"
Solutions
What's New!
Search
"How to Do It"
Solutions
What's New!
Privacy Statement
In-stock orders received before 1 P.M. PST ship same day! Ask about our Nationwide pick up points!
The Yelp reviews below are from paying customers. The reviews are being pulled from an independent 3rd party website. They are real. Click to see more.
Check out Super Soundproofing Co on Yelp
Like Us Facebook
Facebook
Super Soundproofing Privacy Statement by the Super Soundproofing Co™.
Super Soundproofing™’s Privacy Notice
Effective 07/03/2012
Privacy Notice Contents:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available not only on our homepage, but most every page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Super Soundproofing Co™. website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. Some types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we would never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and to protect against hackers.  We do not keep credit cards numbers- they are destroyed at the time of use.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13  and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain at our credit card processors website.  We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 760-752-3030 9-5 Pacific time or send us an email. Or visit us!
BBB Privacy Tips!
0000
Posted in How To Do It
WE HAVE SOLUTIONS!
Please go to the Forum for answers to many questions already answered. (See link on sidebar). We don’t have a technical line anymore.We still answer questions about your purchase as to whether it will do what you expect. Please place your orders in the AM for shipment in the afternoon/next day.
Our soundproofing solutions have helped thousands of our clients! They can work for you, too!
Our walk-in soundproofing store is located at 389 Olive Ave, Vista, Ca. 92083 -- Open weekdays
8-4 'Til Noon on Saturday by appointment only. Location Map & Street View. Nearby Airports: San Diego, Palomar (Carlsbad), (Coaster, too!) Oceanside, Fallbrook, Temecula (Rancho California: French Valley). Call for pickup!
(888) 942-7723
Ph: (760) 752-3030
8-5 Pacific Time. *
FAX: (760)752 3040
E-mail: supersoundproofing@gmail.com
Toll Free
(888) 942-7723
Visit us at: www.soundproofing.org
Super Soundproofing™ | www.soundproofing.org | 389 Olive Ave, Vista, Ca. 92083 | Privacy Statement | Sitemap
